Aleksa Lukić

Date of birth: 03/03/1999 **Address:** Ive Andrića 2, Obrež Email: lukicaleksa04@gmail.com **Telephone:** +381 69 695095



About me

My name is Aleksa. I'm a student on the third year of the University of Metropolitan. During my studies, I gained a lot of practical work in web programming. The projects which I worked with usually have been for clients. It has been a business application or website presentation. Also, I gained an internship within the faculty at the end of the first year in a period of two months. After that, I was hired within RCMT IT Europe for three months in the position of "cybersecurity analyst". More about my project you can find on Github profile or on my website. When I'm not programming I like to relax with friends. In the circle of friends, they consider me a person who always cheers up society. Besides, I love sports, especially table tennis and basketball. Also, a new sport that I like to enjoy is skiing. I like learning new things because that's how I create new ideas.

Work experience

08/2019 - 10/2019 Niš, Srbija

Metropolitan University - IST

• Junior Web Developer

Work on the development of a new student management system

06/2020 - 09/2020 Niš, Srbija

RCMT IT Europe

• Junior Cyber Security Analyst

Education

09/2014 - 05/2018 Varvarin, Srbija

Gymnasium - Mathematics Department

10/2018 - Present Niš, Srbija

Metropolitan University - Software Engineering

The course is intended for the professional study of processes in software system development

References

1. Portfolio

2. Github

General skills

Communication

Problem solving

Teamwork

Attention to details

Skills

- Technologies HTML5/CSS3 Angular 8 SpringBoot JSP Hibernate Node.js TypeORM Nest.js React - Programming languages Java

Javascript

Typescript

- DevOps

Nginx

Redis

My plan in the future to learn these technologies because my plan for a web career is to be a fullstack web developer

Docker/Kubernetes

- UX/UI

Figma

- Version Control

Git